Title: Efficient Development with Cloud Code for Multiple Features  Introduction: This tutorial focuses on utilizing Cloud Code to enhance development speed by managing multiple features concurrently.
By setting up separate instances for different features, conflicts can be avoided, and the development process streamlined.
The tools required are Cloud Code, GitHub, and Superbase.
Prior knowledge of Cloud Code, GitHub, and version control concepts is recommended.
Outcome: At the end of this tutorial, you will have established Cloud Code instances for multiple features, enabling simultaneous work on various aspects of a project without conflicts.
Step-by-step instructions: 1.
Create a directory for 3x development speed:    - Open the terminal and create a new directory named "3x development speed".
- Navigate into the created directory.
2.
Initialize Cloud Code:    - Run the command to initialize Cloud Code in the directory.
- Grant necessary permissions as prompted.
3.
Install necessary MCPs:    - Install the Superbase MCP using the provided command.
- Install the GitHub MCP with the provided command.
- These MCPs allow Cloud Code to interact with Superbase and GitHub.
4.
Define the purpose of each Cloud Code instance:    - Specify the role of each Cloud Code instance in managing GitHub and issues related to different features.
- Highlight the significance of branching in Git to prevent conflicts when working on multiple features simultaneously.
5.
Set up Cloud Code instances for each feature:    - Create separate branches for each feature in your GitHub repository.
- Check out the code into different directories for independent work on each feature.
- Modify the code in each branch separately, resolving conflicts before merging.
6.
Utilize Whisper Flow for collaboration:    - Use Whisper Flow to effectively coordinate and manage development across multiple features.
Final result: By setting up Cloud Code instances for multiple features, you can concurrently work on different aspects of a project.
Utilizing separate branches and directories helps avoid conflicts and accelerates the development process significantly.
This approach enables efficient management and development of multiple features simultaneously, enhancing productivity and efficiency in software development.